Right. Yes. OK, so this
one will. Like I said, I'm not too
worried about right now.
Our access to this we would need right
if we're going to hit the GUI. So
until that's done, we can't do this part
OK?
Internal. Not too concerned about that
because that's for users.
I'm a machine that's SSH,
so these these ones. I've
already submitted a firewall request
for this one. As well.
So this is pretty much your reputation
and all that, right? So yes, this one
covered the DNS that I had referenced
above. What chance is there any umm.
I know you put a star but is is there
a maybe a full list just in case our
network team has an issue with the the
star?I am looking for that right now.
OK. And then this one, is
that this mandatory?Because it looks
like it's just for best practice
information, right?
That URL is just the list that those
systems need to be able to access so
that that URL is an article.
Oh, OK, so let me find out to
make sure because I submitted the article
so that that's not going to work very
well, I guess. But then
you had the port, so that's what confused
me, right?Oh, that's why I
thought you had to hit the URL on
these ports, so OK. I might
have to update this OK.
And then of course, these ones I have not
done yet. So is there anything we can do
in terms of?Setting up
the server still I have.
Local A console access only at this
point. Through the Isla.
Well, not much we can do with that.
Can we possibly I guess set up
the initial IPS? And I was looking
through the article too. I don't know
where you would do the teaming part
of things. Or teaming or
redundancy. Yeah, that was for the next
through.
The. Whatever they tell
management interface is.
As far as the IP addresses, we
can absolutely walk through that text
based menu for each of the agents.
We just can't log into port 10,000
on any agent.
OK, so maybe
that's Eyedrak.
Yes. So
maybe we can do that. All right, let me
pull it up. Yeah, go for it.
Things this one is.
All right, I think I've found a better
article here. I will upload this to.
Archivework Share.
But like a. The roles
that we wanted for are pretty much
identical except for the two I mentioned
where the Sir, I guess the Sir adjust.
Yes, that's going to be
specific to a Sir MGA
implementation.
All right, I've uploaded a new PDF
file. To share
Proofpoint com it is.
Pre installation requirements for on Prem
agents so I think that will also
help in this scenario.
OK.
X3.
Hold on, it's just got hooked up.
OK.
You know, let me let me close up most of
the stuff because it's not showing
properly.
So I'd like to share that exit.
OK.
All right, so the this is the eye track
we're in. I
I was looking at it, I can't find the
teaming part of things that if.
You know what by any chance?
I I do not know.
Where that is.
Let's ask Google.
Well.
Naomi, Nick. Nick. Nick.
Tell Power Edge how to set up Nic teams.
OK, so that's not in idrac.
Philip and Nick came to your house
operating system with Windows Mixed using
the physical Torch.
Under idrax settings, is there a network?
Yeah, there if you go to system you can
see. Network devices,
uh.
Or configuration, yeah.
What's under the contract settings?
Settings OK.
OK, so there. Is just showing the
network settings here, there's no.
No network configuration.
Yeah, this is more for the actual
high track configuration.
Gotcha.
I will. Try
to find that information. OK.
Thank you.
I guess we'll go back to the actual
console. At this point.
Sounds good.
OK.
Are you able to see what I'm sharing
the actual cost itself? OK, good admin
and then password and it will ask you
to change the password on first login.
Yeah, I actually got a little around
there and then it just stopped. So the
yes. Correct.
Uh, OK, I didn't like
it, yes.
Go ahead and do yes, it's going to ask
you some network questions after this.
OK, so give me one second.
Let me grab the IPS.
So this
one should
be 10.10724436.
From that mask was.
All 240.
255258255240 right, That's what
you're saying. Yep.
OK.
Alright.
I think 1 should be fine.
Um, it's a yes or no question.
OK, Yes.
Configuration question Network
2. There you go, there's your
teammate.
Am I going to leave now?
Huh.
We don't actually have an IP for this,
we were doing a false failover.
Or we were expecting to do a fault
tolerant failover at least. That's what
this is. Brian Numer.
If you leave this at yes, basically
network 2 is the failover for network
one, OK? So let's leave it for yes for
now, OK?Sounds good.
I repeat this plank as well.
This is the IP address of the gateway.
Yeah, just need to pull it just to make
sure.
So we've got
a 10.107244 and
33.
Did I step it in wrong? Yeah, I did.
10.107244.
Are you doing and now that's sugary.
So this is the host name without the
fully qualified.
OK, we were giving it this name. Hold
on.
Well, why
did that
happen?
Thank you. It doesn't like the
dashes.
That start with what I'm
thinking letters, numbers and dashes
what you put in.
The main clock.
Oh, the domain name is the domain
portion. So anything
after the host name in the fully
qualified Germanic?
Just for now, all these can be
changed later, right?Yes, OK.
Give me one second, I'm going to pull up
the. Domain server
from something else?
See if that works.
So this is secondary DNS now. If you
don't have one, you can hit enter and
leave it blank. Yeah, I was
supposed to have one but I'm just looking
for. But I might not have it.
Which is kind of silly, but.
OK, well leave it blank for now.
Dictionary, so third.
You've got both name all
right. So now this is the one that we
want, right?
This would be similar to a host file
in Windows where if you wanted to hard
code a DNS override. Yeah,
that's it. Notice
that it requires the IP address first.
Oh.
OK, but. So
do we even get a choice to name the the
server later? Or is this you've already
named it the server you've put in a host
name. This is a host name override.
Oh, I thought, OK, all right then
just enter then I guess, right?
Yes, you can leave that blank.
OK, sure. Yeah, yeah,
right there. Okay. Tertiary
wholesale rights on nothing
here. And.
Confirm. I
think everything looks good.
Yes, for now.
So this will take about 5 minutes.
OK, not sure if you want to.
SSH or connect to any of the
agents and get their unique IP addresses
in there. Yeah, we can
do the next one. We can set it up.
The same thing. Give me a SEC.
So in the I guess the GUI interface is
that where I would be able to add an
extra Nic?
We can sit in the configurations there.
What we have done here, the binding,
we're just telling.
ES0 ETH zero to be mirrored
by ETH one.
Question as well.
You know it. It escapes me right now.
Give me a second.
Let me just set up the third one and see,
OK?
Oh.
OK.
Looking back to Leo. Is there
any known issues with the integrated and
the?The
actual.
Board, I guess the expansion Nicks.
The only reason why? Yeah, because
the only reason why I'm asking
is that another vendor which is
similar, let's put it that way.
I was told that they had
issues where when it booting up,
things would automatically go to the
integrated. Nick, rather
than the.
The I guess the expansion
ports Nick. Gotcha.
Yeah, I'm not sure on that.
OK, let me go back to the original
server. Give me a SEC.
OK.
Should I?
I guess what are we supposed to do
here, if anything?
Nothing. This is just the default admin
screen. OK, you can. You can do option
5 and then option 8 for the command line.
Option 5.
And.
OK. Is there anything else we can do on
these servers or is that pretty much
everything right now since we don't have
access to the?
Admin interface, Yeah, everything from
here on needs to be through the GUI.
That would be.
Setting up a license ID and registering
the config master, ensuring that we can
log into that and then adding agents from
that GUI.
OK, I guess that's
it for now.
I just typed back to it. Yes, that
will bring you back to that menu.
OK, return to. I actually wanted to
see what.
This option is.
Just shows you what the network settings
are. Doesn't that change anything?
It's.
There should be a menu option to go
through that initial. Text based menu
again. OK, if that's
option one.
Setup agent.
And then else we just go through the
exact same thing again. It does
the exact same thing we just walked
through. Yes, if we ever wanted to like
reset everything actually there, there's
not much so the name of the IP
use so. If we, I
guess. If we accidentally
logged in to the agent.
And it became a master. How will we reset
that?There
is a command line option that is
theoretically usable. I would recommend
just redeploying the ISO file.
OK, so. OK, so
there's no like command prompt that we
can do to just wipe and go back to
default. There kind of is, but the
ISO is going to be a lot easier.
OK. All right, I
guess I'm good for now until
we get the admin access and
the hopefully the. Degree
Communication port. To
get the license that's part of the.
The dot proof point right for the light
sensing as well. Yes. OK, OK.
I guess I'm good for
now. OK. Were there
other questions or other areas that
people wanted to ask about or were
discussed?I have the one, but
I'll wait. Go for it. No, no, go for it.
I'm good at this point. So
this is something I'm going to
figure out once we're set up
for the portals soon for the
SER and also for SEG. But
if you recall few meetings ago,
we discussed how SEG is separate
from SER and for logging into
the secure portals for both of
these. They're separate, so there's
one URL for SCR and there's another
URL for seg.
My question is like. If
I send a. If I send an
encrypted e-mail through an application
to an external user. Once they
click on that link, they log into the
portal. Let's say everything is set up so
they log into the portal. But for the
very first e-mail, I believe they have to
register. So they answer some security
questions, perhaps even picket password
in order to log in next time. That's my
assumption. So once they set once they're
set up on the SER.
Does this mean this is the
same?Registration process.
That also satisfies the seg or
no if a user sends an
encrypted e-mail from TD to them.
Then because they go to a different
URL on seg this time they have
to again register. I'm hoping
they can. They are separate portals.
Technically OK. So I'm just
wondering like do you guys have any
plans in future to kind of merge
them together so that way you know,
because I'm assuming external, external
users don't necessarily. Understand, you
know, they just see an e-mail came from
TD and you know, they log in, they
register and then they can read and maybe
the next time they get another app
e-mail, they can just log in no problem.
But if a user sends them an e-mail,
they're not going to pay that much
attention to the fact that oh, this is a
user versus the other one was an app.
They may think, oh, how come I have to
register again and open a ticket? Do you
guys have any plans in future to kind of?
Merge these two in a way so
that you know each individual out there
on the Internet only registers with
Proofpoint once. I
end up with one account product, future
plans. I would highly recommend going
into our support portal and opening up
in RFE for that feature. Or
something like that. OK. OK.
Actually, is there any way to you? Iknow.
It's the same idea. Is there any way to
use the same?Umm.
Secure.
Component A security component, Uh.
Yes. There's a couple
of different methods we can discuss them.
One is called Trusted Partner encryption
where you essentially authorize one
cluster to be able to use a
different clusters decrypt keys. The
other would be anything that is going
to get encrypted we can route them
all through the same portal.
And that way there's only one login.
OK, because I probably. We'll,
we'll discuss this with Daniel and of
course Jet and anyone else if their
decision makers. But now that sounds
more. Yeah, no, because I think you
bring up a good point. Because let's say
if I log, I get one e-mail, I create
a password and then I'm not going to pay
attention to, you know, it being from a
different link or whatnot. And you know,
I wouldn't want to sign up for a second
time type thing. And you may not even
like the fact that, you know, there are
two separate passwords and you don't know
which one to use for which, right?Yeah,
exactly, because then I put in the wrong
password and I get locked out.
Picking it, that's the correct one. And
yeah, it's a good point actually.
So Dan, we will take you on up on
that to set it up in a way that
there's only one login for users of SEC
and SER. We'll discuss it once
I set up the sub domain, of course, OK?
Thank you. Yeah, of course.
Anything else for anybody I'll discuss
today. They get much
further on those rules if anything or I I
have not had time the last day and a half
to to take a look at that. I do have some
time booked out for tomorrow for it.
OK.
I'm good so far until I get
access to the actual console and play
around with it. I.
I don't think I'll have much more right
now. Understood. If you want to have a
separate session for just the SCR Gateway
or SCR MTA setup. Once you do get
access, I would recommend using my
calendar link and just grab whatever
available time you can. OK.
And you're going to send me the?
I have doubted that
to share.proofpoint.com already. OK,
let me look anyway.
Do you have any documentation on the
actual configuration of the?
I guess the fault.
Never set up. I am looking for
that currently. OK.
And also, if you can, something about
additional Nicks as well.
While you're looking for it. Yep, and
anything I can find for physical
appliance mix I will get to you.
Sounds good. OK, good. Good.
All right. Does that appreciate the time
everybody, if nobody has anything else,
but I am happy to field any other topics
or questions.
Doesn't sound like it. OK,
OK. Thank you very much.
Meet the next little bit.
Thank you all. You should have.
Thank you. Bye. Bye. Thank you.
Right.
Yeah.